[SPEAKER_00 | 0.72]
What you out of here doing man?
[SPEAKER_00 | 0.84]
Come over here and talk to me.
[Target_Speaker | 0.36]
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
[Target_Speaker | 0.35]
Why are you going to touch me?
[Target_Speaker | weak 0.30]
What's going on?
[SPEAKER_00 | 0.68]
Come over here and talk to me.
[SPEAKER_00 | 0.47]
You are on private property.
[Target_Speaker | 0.67]
I'm not going to go in there.
[SPEAKER_00 | 0.74]
You are on private property.
[SPEAKER_00 | 0.67]
Do not tell me what you're not going to do.
[SPEAKER_00 | 1.00]
Do you have any weapons on you?
[Target_Speaker | weak 0.20]
Nope.
[SPEAKER_00 | 0.91]
Do you mind if I pat you down to shake?
[Target_Speaker | weak 0.30]
Yeah, I do.
[SPEAKER_00 | 0.61]
Okay, why are you out here?
[Target_Speaker | 0.55]
This is an illegal search and seizure.
[SPEAKER_00 | 0.74]
Why are you out here?
[Target_Speaker | 0.79]
I'm invoking my 5th Amendment rights.
[SPEAKER_00 | 0.57]
You want to give me a reason why you're here?
[Target_Speaker | 0.68]
Where you took me from was public property.
[Target_Speaker | 0.36]
I'm going to invoke my 5th Amendment rights to pass out.
[SPEAKER_00 | 0.89]
You're being arrested for criminal loitering.
[SPEAKER_00 | 0.67]
Criminal loitering?
[SPEAKER_00 | 0.41]
You can't give me a reason why you're out here.
[Target_Speaker | 0.71]
Am I being arrested or detained?
[SPEAKER_00 | 0.73]
You're being arrested.
[SPEAKER_00 | weak 0.30]
Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_00 | 0.76]
He's gotta write the videos.
[SPEAKER_00 | 0.63]
[SPEAKER_00 | 0.72]
He said you refused to answer any questions.
[Target_Speaker | 0.94]
Do you actually believe I have to give you a reason why
I'm standing on a public
[Target_Speaker | 0.94]
sidewalk?
[SPEAKER_00 | 0.63]
Oh, 100%.
[Target_Speaker | weak 0.30]
Really?
Yeah.
[Target_Speaker | 0.75]
Looks like the guys need some training.
[SPEAKER_00 | 1.00]
If you get out and do the same thing over again, the same
thing's gonna happen.
[Target_Speaker | weak 0.30]
We'll see.
[Target_Speaker | weak 0.25]
We'll see you later.
[Target_Speaker | weak 0.30]
Take care.
[Target_Speaker | weak 0.25]
What's going on today, everybody?
[Target_Speaker | 1.00]
As you may know, earlier this year, I was arrested in
Tupelo, Mississippi
[Target_Speaker | 1.00]
on charges that did not even exist.
This is going to be the story behind how the arresting
officer explained and
[Target_Speaker | 1.00]
demonstrated his own downfall in this situation and how he
explained he
[Target_Speaker | 1.00]
even knew he was incorrect.
[Target_Speaker | 0.87]
And that's not even the craziest part.
[Target_Speaker | 1.00]
But now that my lawyer has gotten the case dismissed and
all the charges are
[Target_Speaker | 1.00]
dismissed, I am free to talk about the entire situation
and show all of the
[Target_Speaker | 1.00]
evidence that I have gotten through the discovery period
in this case.
[Target_Speaker | 1.00]
But as you guys know, with this false arrest and the rest
of the process coming up
[Target_Speaker | 1.00]
afterwards, it is a long,
and arduous road ahead of me.
[Target_Speaker | 1.00]
And with YouTube demonetizing 99% of First Amendment
auditors
[Target_Speaker | 1.00]
out there, it would be a fantastic time to go and find me
on my other
[Target_Speaker | 1.00]
platforms.
I am on Rumble, I am on Patreon, I am on Locals.
[Target_Speaker | 0.78]
All of those will be linked in the description.
[Target_Speaker | 1.00]
And just a watch and a follow is greatly appreciated.
But if you are in the position to do so, my Venmo and my
PayPal and my
[Target_Speaker | 1.00]
other donation